.
.
Sir, Miss Su's father is here to see you with fruit.
سيدي ، والد الآنسة سو هنا لرؤيتك مع الفاكهة.
Please come in.
تفضل بالدخول.
Mr. Leng,
السيد.  لينغ ،
Uncle,
عم،
No respect, no respect.
لا احترام ولا احترام.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
Have a seat.
تفضل بالجلوس.
Mr. Leng,
السيد.  لينغ ،
since we last met,
منذ آخر لقاء لنا ،
I've been thinking about it,
كنت أفكر في ذلك ،
so I came to recognize you.
لذلك جئت للتعرف عليك.
Uncle,
عم،
looking at your sad face,
بالنظر إلى وجهك الحزين ،
Did something happen to you?
هل حدث لك شيء؟
Look.
ينظر.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
I can't hide it from Mr. Leng.
لا أستطيع إخفاءه عن السيد لينغ.
I'm really sorry.
أنا حقا آسف.
Uncle is really in trouble.
العم حقا في ورطة.
That's why I came to you.
لهذا السبب جئت اليك.
Uncle, if you need anything, just tell me.
عمي ، إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء ، فقط أخبرني.
I will help you.
سوف اساعدك.
Uncle knows,
العم يعلم ،
the money you gave me last time,
المال الذي أعطيتني إياه آخر مرة ،
For Su Li's sake,
من أجل سو لي ،
what about me?
ماذا عني؟
But,
لكن،
Uncle,
عم،
I'm sorry, Su Li.
أنا آسف ، سو لي.
I want to pay back all my gambling debts.
أريد أن أسدد جميع ديون القمار.
With the money you gave me?
بالمال الذي أعطيته لي؟
Gambling again.
القمار مرة أخرى.
I just want to
أريد فقط
put this money,
ضع هذا المال ،
Get them all back.
استعدهم جميعًا.
But I didn't expect
لكني لم أتوقع
to lose all of them.
لتفقدهم جميعًا.
Uncle, there's really nothing I can do.
عمي ، لا يوجد شيء يمكنني فعله حقًا.
That's why I came to you.
لهذا السبب جئت اليك.
Uncle,
عم،
I know everything.
انا أعرف كل شيء.
You don't have to say anything.
ليس عليك قول أي شيء.
As long as it's something that can be solved with money,
طالما أنه شيء يمكن حله بالمال ،
it's not a problem.
ليست مشكلة.
Take the money first.
خذ المال أولاً.
Well
حسنًا
Uncle, yes.
العم نعم.
May I ask you,
هل لي أن أسألك،
how are you going to repay me?
كيف ستدفع لي؟
Mr. Leng,
السيد.  لينغ ،
tell me. I'll do it.
أخبرني.  سأفعل ذلك.
Anything will do.
اي شيء سيفعل.
Yes.
نعم.
I asked you to get something
لقد طلبت منك الحصول على شيء
from Miss Su for me.
من الآنسة سو بالنسبة لي.
I don't like forcing others.
لا أحب إجبار الآخرين.
It's all up to you,
الامر يرجع لك،
uncle.
عم.
No, I won't.
لا ، لن أفعل.
What do you want me to take, Mr. Leng?
ماذا تريد مني أن آخذ ، سيد لينج؟
Look,
ينظر،
Uncle,
عم،
there's 1 million here.
هناك مليون هنا.
500thousand, you take it to pay off your debts first.
500 ألف ، تأخذها لسداد ديونك أولاً.
All you need to do is to bring the Heart of Stallone,
كل ما عليك فعله هو إحضار قلب ستالون ،
and agree to our marriage.
ونوافق على زواجنا.
Not to mention the Heart of Stallone,
ناهيك عن قلب ستالون ،
you just want the stars in the sky.
أنت فقط تريد النجوم في السماء.
I'll pick it for you, too.
سأختاره لك أيضًا.
Don't worry,
لا تقلق،
about what you've told me,
حول ما قلته لي ،
Uncle, I will never refuse.
عمي ، لن أرفض أبدًا.
Yes, yes, yes.
نعم نعم نعم.
Don't worry. It's my pleasure
لا تقلق.  انه لمن دواعي سروري
to work with Mr. Leng.
للعمل مع السيد لينغ.
Since you've admired my daughter
منذ أن كنت معجبة بابنتي
for a long time.
لفترة طويلة.
Then I'll decide for Su Li.
ثم سأقرر ل Su Li.
I'll marry Su Li to you.
سوف أتزوج سو لي لك.
I'll take the money first.
سآخذ المال أولاً.
Think of it as ordering money.
فكر في الأمر على أنه طلب نقود.
Uncle,
عم،
keep your word,
احفظ كلمتك
It's a deal.
انها صفقة.
One family,
عائلة واحدة،
one family, come here,
عائلة واحدة تعال هنا
Uncle's family.
عائلة العم.
Come on.
تعال.
Have some tea.
لديك بعض الشاي.
Su Shengnan,
سو شنغنان ،
don't leave such low-grade shower gel
لا تترك جل الاستحمام منخفض الدرجة
at home from now on.
في المنزل من الآن فصاعدًا.
Got it?
فهمتها؟
Miss Leng,
ملكة جمال لينغ ،
there are some things that can clean your body.
هناك بعض الأشياء التي يمكن أن تنظف جسمك.
There's no distinction between high and low, Brother,
لا فرق بين العالي والمنخفض يا أخي
why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Brother Feng,
الأخ فنغ ،
Shengnan,
شينغنان ،
Yes.
نعم.
Look, I brought someone here
انظر ، أحضرت شخصًا إلى هنا
to see your daughter,
لترى ابنتك ،
If Mr. Leng hadn't led me,
إذا لم يقودني السيد لينغ ،
I wouldn't have found you.
لم أكن لأجدك.
You live such a good life.
أنت تعيش مثل هذه الحياة الجيدة.
As a father,
كأب ،
I'm satisfied.
أنا راضٍ.
This guy,
هذا الشخص،
why are you two together?
لماذا انتما الاثنان معا
Shengnan,
شينغنان ،
don't be angry.
لا تغضب.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
It was uncle who found me.
كان عمي من وجدني.
Then he proposed
ثم اقترح
to me,
إلي